fforfree.net 2013-01-15

# Privacy Policy. ~ FforFree.net - Worldwide Free Stuff, Contests, Deals, Sweepstakes, Prizes, India Free Stuff, News.

##  [Privacy Policy.](http://www.fforfree.net/p/privacy-policy.html)

#### Do you like this ?

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, [www.fforfree.net](http://www.fforfree.net/) have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
  * [www.fforfree.net](http://www.fforfree.net/) will not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. 
  * Please note that www.fforfree.net contains links to other web sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage our users to be aware that when they leave our site that you read the privacy statements of each web site that might collect personally identifying information.
  * This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by  www.fforfree.net If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact: **info@fforfree.net**
  * We welcome all of you sharing our content on your blog, but make sure you specify a backlink to our blog www.fforfree.net, that's the only condition.
